FAISHAL PRATAMA

H. Liun Street No. 86a Petukangan Utara, Pesanggrahan, Jakarta Selatan, 12260 | 085156325387 | faishalprtm@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I have a bachelor's degree in criminology with experience in evaluation and collaboration as well as customer service experience in handling social media and also experience as a recruiter partnering with a national bank. Currently I am working in the field of journalism as a radio reporter. After working in the field of journalism, I was very interested in getting involved in online media. I am an ambitious person, adaptable and always learn what I am passionate about.

Education

Bachelor of Social Science: Criminology

2022

Universitas Budi Luhur GPA: 3 67/4 00 Jakarta, Indonesia

Experience

Radio Reporter

11/2023 to Current Jakarta, Indonesia

PT. Radio Elshinta

- · Carrying out reports to the field
- Perform Voice Over for sound fragments to the Radio
- Carry out transcripts on issues being worked on
- · Edit the results of voice overs and inserts from sources in sound editing applications
- · Send finished voice over results to email
- Prepped and delivered up-to-date regional weather information
- Presented informative local traffic and travel updates
- Spoke clearly and eloquently for full audience understanding

HR Recruiter

03/2023 to 09/2023

PT. Padma Raharja Sentosa

Jakarta, Indonesia

- Manage job portals for hiring needs
 - · Communicate regarding the required candidate to the user
- Conduct online/offline interviews according to hiring needs
- · Manage the process of filing candidates who pass the interview stage
- · Doing daily, weekly and monthly reports regarding candidates invited and accepted for work

Collaboration and Evaluation (Internship) Ditjenpas Kemenkumham RI

03/2021 to 07/2021 Jakarta, Indonesia

- Make minutes of cooperation meetings with related institutions
- · Making monthly reports related to the results of cooperation agreements with related institutions
- Archiving agreement documents in accordance with the theme of the cooperation agreement meeting

Customer Service Social Media

10/2016 to 12/2016 Jakarta. Indonesia

PT. Akulaku Silvrr Indonesia

Follow up customer complaints on the company's Facebook platform

- · Resolving customer complaints or problems
- · Make monthly reports related to customer activities and complaints
- Provide feedback on the efficiency of the customer service process
- . Following up with the merchant regarding problems with the goods purchased by the customer

Professional Skills

- · MS. Office
- Problem Solving
- Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Analytical Skills
- Teamwork
- Recruitment
- HR knowledge

- Customer Support
- Broadcast Journalism
- SEO (Search Engine Optimization)
- Voiceovers
- On Air Reporting
- Transcription
- · Radio Presenting
- Voice Editing

Social Media

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/faishalprtm/